

# Moskalenko Dmitry

Front End Developer

+380 505 634 338

fe.jimmy.co@gmail.com 🔀

Dnipro O



## Summary

A passionate junior front-end developer with a strong desire to learn and thrive in a collaborative team setting. Eagerly pursuing fresh opportunities and challenges that will not only broaden my skill set but also bring a motivated specialist to your company. Backed by both commercial and non-commercial experience in website development.

#### **Skills**

- HTML5 / CSS(SCSS)
- JavaScript (ES6+)
- React + Typescript
- Redux / RTK
- CSS Modules / Tailwind
- NextJS
- Nodeis (Express / NestJS)
- PostgreSQL / MongoDb

## Work experience

05.2023 - 08.2023 Trainee Full Stack Developer

#### **AmconSoft**

Full-stack development of an E-commerce project in collaboration with a team of developers.

Stack: NextJs / NestJs / PostgreSQL

09.2022 - 12.2022 Front-End Developer

#### Freelance with coach

- Collaborated with the coach to design new features for web application.
- Created an interactive map and chat for clients. Stack React / Typescript / Redux-Toolkit / Firebase / Mapbox.
- •Maintenance of code, debugging and solving client/server side problems

03.2019 - 02.2022 Sales manager / Acting director Company LLC 'ALLO'

## Languages

Ukrainian - native Russian - native English - A2

#### Education

2015 - 2019 National Technical University Dnipro Polytechnic

Bachelor Degree Field of study Mining. Professional qualification "Specialist in the field of mining"

## **Additional contacts**

**Telegramm** Linkedin

# Work arrangement

- Remote
- Office-based
- Open to both remote and office-based work

https://github.com/DmitryMass GitHub:

Portfolio: <a href="https://jimmyco-portfolio.netlify.app/">https://jimmyco-portfolio.netlify.app/</a>

#### **Certificates**

Front end Basic course Front end Advanced course **English** course

